Q1: difference between undefined and null data type?
A1: undefined means a variable has been declared but has not yet been assigned a value like 0.
undefined and null are two distinct types: undefined is a type itself (undefined) while null is an object.

q2: when the output will be null ?
When defining a variable that is meant to later hold an object, it is advisable to initialize the variable to null.

q3: what is the hoisting ?
Hoisting is JavaScript's default behavior of moving all declarations to the top of the current scope (to the top of the current script or the current function).

q4: what difference between var , let, const ?

• 1- var declarations are globally scoped or function scoped while let and const are block scoped.
• 2- var and let can be declared without being initialized, const must be initialized during declaration.
• 3- var variables can be updated and re-declared within its scope; let variables can be updated but not re-declared; const variables can neither be updated nor re-declared.
• 4- They are all hoisted to the top of their scope. But while var variables are initialized with undefined, let and const variables are not initialized.
